<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Intents and Widgets</string>
    <string-array name="spinnerArray">
        <item>Golden State Warriors</item>
        <item>Los Angeles Lakers</item>
        <item>Chicago Bulls</item>
        <item>Cleveland Cavaliers</item>
        <item>San Antonio Spurs</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="object_image">
        <item>@drawable/golden</item>
        <item>@drawable/lakers</item>
        <item>@drawable/bulls</item>
        <item>@drawable/cleveland</item>
        <item>@drawable/spurs</item>

    </integer-array>


    <string name="desc">The Golden State Warriors are an American professional basketball
        team based in Oakland, California. The Warriors compete in the National Basketball
        Association (NBA) as a member club of the leagues Western Conference Pacific Division.
        The team was established in 1946 as the Philadelphia Warriors based in Philadelphia,
        Pennsylvania, a founding member of the Basketball Association of America (BAA),
        and it won the inaugural 1947 BAA Finals that is now considered the first NBA Championship.\n \n Current Players : \n \n Leandro Barbosa \n
    Harrison Barnes \n Andrew Bogut \n Ian Clark \n Stephen Curry \n Festus Ezeli
    </string>


    <string name="desc3">The Chicago Bulls are an American professional basketball team based in Chicago,
        Illinois. The Bulls compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member team of the league
        s Eastern Conference Central Division. The team was founded on January 16, 1966. The team play their home
        games at the United Center, an arena shared with the Chicago Blackhawks of the National Hockey League (NHL).
        The Bulls saw their greatest success during the 1990s. They are known for having one of the NBAs greatest
        dynasties, winning six NBA championships between 1991 and 1998 with two three-peats. All six championship
        teams were led by Hall of Famers Michael Jordan, Scottie Pippen and coach Phil Jackson. The Bulls are the
        only NBA franchise to win multiple championships and never lose an NBA Finals series in their history.\n \n Current Players :
    \n \n Cameron Bairstow \n Aaron Brooks \n Jimmy Butler \n Mike Dunleavy \n Cristiano Felicio \n Pau Gasol</string>

    <string name="desc2">The Los Angeles Lakers are an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles, California,
        that competes in the National Basketball Association (NBA). They are members of the Pacific Division of the leagues Western Conference.
        The Lakers play their home games at Staples Center, an arena shared with the NBAs Los Angeles Clippers, the Los Angeles Sparks of the
        Womens National Basketball Association, and the Los Angeles Kings of the National Hockey League.[3] The Lakers are one of the most successful
        teams in the history of the NBA, and have won 16 NBA championships, their last being in 2010. As of 2015, the Lakers are the second most valuable
        franchise in the NBA according to Forbes, having an estimated value of $2.7 billion. \n \n Current Players : \n \n
    Brandon Bass \n Tarik Black \n Anthony Brown \n Kobe Bryant \n Jordan Clarkson \n Roy Hibbert</string>

    <string name="desc4">The Cleveland Cavaliers, also known as the Cavs, are an American professional basketball team
        based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Cavaliers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the
        leagues Eastern Conference Central Division. The Cavaliers are the only remaining charter member of the
        division (all the other Central Division teams joined later from the now-defunct Midwest Division). \n The team began
        play in the league in 1970 as an expansion team. Home games are played at Quicken Loans Arena, which the team shares
        with the Cleveland Gladiators of the Arena Football League, and the Lake Erie Monsters of the American Hockey League.
        Past NBA greats such as Nate Thurmond, Lenny Wilkens, Walt Clyde Frazier, and Shaquille O Neal have also played in Cleveland.
        \n \n Current Players : \n \n Kyrie Irving \n LeBron James \n Channing Frye \n Timofey Mozgov \n Kevin Love \n Iman Shumpert</string>

    <string name="desc5">The San Antonio Spurs are an American professional basketball team based in San Antonio, Texas.
        They are part of the Southwest Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA). \n
The Spurs are one of four former American Basketball Association teams to remain intact in the NBA after the 1976 ABA–NBA
        merger and the only former ABA team to have won an NBA championship. The Spurs five NBA championships are the fourth
        most in history behind only the Boston Celtics (17), Los Angeles Lakers (16), and Chicago Bulls (6). The Spurs currently
        rank first among active franchises for the highest winning percentage in NBA history, and are the only team in the NBA with
        a tied or better head-to-head regular season record against every active NBA franchise. \n \n Current Players :
    \n \n LaMarcus Aldridge \n Kyle Anderson \n Matt Bonner \n Rasual Butler \n Boris Diaw \n Tim Duncan</string>

</resources>
